A high-fit tender appears with one week left.
The team must decide, reconstruct requirements,
coordinate the response,
and catch every amendment before submission.
TenderGraph is an agentic tender operating system
for the complete workflow.
Seven bounded agents cover the full bidding
lifecycle.
A human qualification gate unlocks the bid plan.
Two unresolved requirements still block compliance.
No agent can release the bid.
New evidence replans only the affected work.
The operating layer is proven against a
hash-verified public evaluation.
Every conclusion is bound to exact evidence.
The inspector exposes source, page, quotation,
parser, authority, URL, and hash.
A commission recommendation is not a signed
contract.
The question runs through ChatGPT-authenticated
Codex without an API key.
GPT-5.6 composes only from admitted claims.
The trace retains the model and Session ID.
Fifteen code-owned gates reject invention, evidence
swaps, scope contamination,
leakage, and incomplete output.
A new official PDF becomes hashed, addressable
evidence.
It does not automatically become authority.
Codex compares the update with every active
conclusion.
Six gates validate scope, evidence, complete impact,
action semantics, and shadow authority.
Nothing changes before human review.
A corrective resolution is the harder test.
The original winner and loss explanation change.
The award rule remains valid.
The result matches the versioned reference and
cannot promote itself.
The enforcement is measured: 49 tests and 23 golden
scenarios.
It includes 6 lifecycle, 15 composition, and 6
impact gates.
The harness admitted 0 of 8 injected faults.
This capture retains three real Codex Session IDs.
Codex accelerated architecture, implementation,
testing, and production diagnosis.
TenderGraph gives companies an agentic bidding team
with governed memory.
Agents can discover, qualify, prepare, check,
monitor, and learn.
GPT-5.6 can reason. Humans remain the authority.